MATEUSZ K. WOJNO

ASPIRING PROGRAMMER

ABOUT ME







mateusz.k.wojno@gmail.com

Bialystok/Warsaw

My first programming journey started relatively recently. I am thousands of lines of code away from writing my first words in the IDE. The first "Hello World," which once delighted me, today amuses me. I know that I've just seen the top of the Iceberg. So I would like to gain the necessary experience as a trainee under the watchful eye of more advanced programmers.

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS basics
- Linux, Bash basics
- C# basics
- Python basics
- Problem-Solving
- Algorithms basics
- Git basics
- English B2

EDUCATION

MASTER OF LAW

University of Bialystok (2016-2021)

COMPUTER SCIENCE
ITC AND PROGRAMMING
(POSTGRADUATE)

Bialystok University of Technology (2022-present)

EXPERIENCE

RETURN TO GIPATH - EVIL ISLANDS MOD

Evil Island Curse of the Lost Soul - multiplayer experience improved 2021-Present

I've figured out what certain entries in the game database are responsible for. Then I made many quality of life changes. The game pace was too slow - so i fixed that as well as many many more issues like too weak enemies and almost no treasures unlike in the single player mode. I love this game due to its unique crafting system, so I have improved it too. In this mod you can enhance your weapons with stronger spells which have also aoe effect (unlike before)

Some changes I did in collaboration with my mate @Formcaster. Check out short demo - link in the header.

WDB - VBA EXCEL MACROS

Macros which automates tedious accounting processes

17-10-2022 - 19-10-2022

I have used VBA, Excel, PowerQuery and USB stick to automate process of entering production reports to Excel. Automation is almost fully. Today the same tasks can be done in 90% less time than before.

Link in the header.